<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on English 5IB</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/</link><description>Recent content in Home on English 5IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alpha Go</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/alpha-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/alpha-go/</guid><description>Alpha GO A computer program called AlphaGo has beaten Lee Sedol, a master player In the ancient Chinese board game of Go in a landmark moment for AI.
In Go two player take turns in placing black or white stones on a 19-by-19 grid. To win you need to surround your opponent&amp;rsquo;s pieces. It is a more complex challenge for a computer than chess - there are more possible positions in Go than atoms in the universe - and players rely on human instinct as much as strategy.</description></item><item><title>DBMS</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/dbms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/dbms/</guid><description>Database Management System A database management system (DB/MS) can store, edit and organise
It stores data in one central location It control who can access and edit the data. It allows data to be shared by many users. It provides user interfaces to work with the data. It automatically creates backups of the datal. DBMS offers many significant benefits.
Security: the data is in a safe central location and different access rights can be given to different people.</description></item><item><title>Definition</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/definition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/definition/</guid><description>What is artificial intelligence? Artificial Intelligence (AI) involves using computers to do things that traditionally require human intelligence. This means creating algorithms to classify, analyze, and draw predictions from data. It also involves acting on data, learning from new data, and improving over time.
&amp;ldquo;Every aspect of learning or any other feature of intelligence can in principle be so precisely described that a machine can be made to simulate it.</description></item><item><title>Examples</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/examples/</guid><description>Some examples Amazon GO Amazon Go is a chain of convenience stores in the United States and the United Kingdom, operated by the online retailer Amazon. The stores are cashierless, thus partially automated, with customers able to purchase products without being checked out by a cashier or using a self-checkout station.Amazon uses several technologies to automate Go stores, including computer vision, deep learning algorithms, and sensor fusion for the purchase, checkout, and payment steps associated with a retail transaction.</description></item><item><title>Life</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/turing/life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/turing/life/</guid><description>Alan Turing&amp;rsquo;s life Alan Turing is often described as the father of modern computer science. His idea of creating a machine to turn thought processes into numbers was a turning
point in the history of computers.
Turing, born in London in 1912, developed some of his most significant theories while studying mathematics at Cambridge in the 1930s. However, despite his brilliance, he suffered from a feeling of isolation, and found it difficult to make friends.</description></item><item><title>Robots</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/robots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/artificial-intelligence/robots/</guid><description>Will Robots take our jobs?
What is unpredictable about recent technological changes? What kind of jobs will go?</description></item><item><title>The Databases</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/the-databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/the-databases/</guid><description>The Databases A database is a way of storing large quantities of information so that, using a computer, it can be
searched: to find specific data. sorted (i.e, organised in different ways): to compare data and create reports. Databases have become essential in many different areas of modern life from government and business to science and education. Tax authorities, for example, use databases to keep records of taxpayers and payments, businesses use them to keep customer account and schools use them to maintain student records.</description></item><item><title>Turing Test</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/turing/turing-test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/turing/turing-test/</guid><description>
The Turing test: Can a computer pass for a human?
How does the Turing test work? What are the problems with this test?</description></item></channel></rss>