<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cybersecurity on English 5IB</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/</link><description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on English 5IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Computer Hacking</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/computer-hacking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/computer-hacking/</guid><description>Computer Hacking It is a practice of modifying computer hardware and software to accomplish a goal outside the creator’s original purpose. The purpose of hacking a computer system may vary from simply demonstrations of the technical ability, to stealing, modifying or destroying information for social, economic or political reasons. Now corporations are hiring hackers, people who are engaged in hacking computers with the purpose to hack the computer of an organization and to find and fix security vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>Creating and distributing viruses over internet</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/creating-and-distributing-viruses-over-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/creating-and-distributing-viruses-over-internet/</guid><description>Creating and distributing viruses over internet Spreading of a virus can cause business and financial loss to an organization. The loss includes the cost of repairing the system, cost associated with the loss of business during downtime and cost of loss of opportunity. If the organization finds the hacker, it can sue him for the sum of more than or equivalent to the loss borne by the organization.
Spamming Sending of unsolicited and commercial bulk message over the internet is known as spamming.</description></item><item><title>Malware and its type</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/malware-and-its-type/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/malware-and-its-type/</guid><description>Malware and its type Malware stands for “Malicious Software” and it is designed to gain access or installed into the computer without the consent of the user. They perform unwanted tasks in the host computer for the benefit of a third party. There is a full range of malwares which can seriously degrade the performance of the host machine. Some of these go from simply distracting/annoying the user, to more complex or harmful actions which capture sensitive data from the host machine and send it to remote servers.</description></item><item><title>What's a Cyber Crime</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/whats-a-cyber-crime/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/cybersecurity/whats-a-cyber-crime/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s a Cyber Crime Introduction to cyber crime The internet was born around 1960‟s where its access was limited to a few scientists, researchers and the Defense only. Initially computer criminals’ purpose was only meant to damage computers and related infrastructure. Around 1980‟s the trend changed from damaging the machine to causing a computer malfunction using a malicious code called virus. Till then the effect was not so widespread because Internet was only confined to defense setups, large international companies and research communities.</description></item></channel></rss>