<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Artificial Intelligences on English 5IB</title><link>http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/</link><description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligences on English 5IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Definition</title><link>http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/definition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/definition/</guid><description>What is artificial intelligence? Artificial Intelligence (AI) involves using computers to do things that traditionally require human intelligence. This means creating algorithms to classify, analyze, and draw predictions from data. It also involves acting on data, learning from new data, and improving over time.
&amp;ldquo;Every aspect of learning or any other feature of intelligence can in principle be so precisely described that a machine can be made to simulate it.</description></item><item><title>Examples</title><link>http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/docs/artificial-intelligence/examples/</guid><description>Some examples Amazon GO Amazon Go is a chain of convenience stores in the United States and the United Kingdom, operated by the online retailer Amazon. The stores are cashierless, thus partially automated, with customers able to purchase products without being checked out by a cashier or using a self-checkout station.Amazon uses several technologies to automate Go stores, including computer vision, deep learning algorithms, and sensor fusion for the purchase, checkout, and payment steps associated with a retail transaction.</description></item></channel></rss>