<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming Languages on English 5IB</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/</link><description>Recent content in Programming Languages on English 5IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Application Programming</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/application-programming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/application-programming/</guid><description>Application Programming Application software is usually created by systems analysts and computer programmers. The system analyst studies the particular requirements and objectives of the potential users and decides what the software should do. The programmers then write the detailed programs based on these guidelines, which are often a combination of databases and algorithms. Databases consist of the information that the program processes. Algorithms are the sequences of steps that the program follows to process this intormation.</description></item><item><title>Computer Languages</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/computer-languages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/computer-languages/</guid><description>Computer Languages Why do we need computer languages?
Computers understand only machine language, the binary stream of Os and 1s, which is difficult for us humans to comprehend. So programming languages were devised so that we can interact with our computers in a more natural way. There are two types of programming language: low-level and high-level.
Low-level languages are based on commands very similar to those that are understood by the CPU itself.</description></item><item><title>Programming Languages</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/programming-languages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/programming-languages/</guid><description>Programming Languages most in demand Many top jobs in technology now require programming skills and so learning how to code can be a real career boost, but what is the best programming language to learn? The following list, based on databases of job vacancies for computer programmers, shows the programming languages most requested by employers. Choice of languages varies according to employiment sector. Banking systems need to perform complicated functions with minimal latency, requiring a language such as C++.</description></item><item><title>System Software</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/system-software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/ko/en/docs/programming-languages/system-software/</guid><description>System Software The software of a computer consists of the programs which tell the hardware what to do. There are two basic types: system software and application software, System software is a permanent component of the computer that controls essential functions and provides a platform for application software. Application software is user-oriented: it enables users to perform specific tasks such as editing a document or browsing the web. It relies on, and runs within, the environment provided by the system software.</description></item></channel></rss>