<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Databases on English 5IB</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/</link><description>Recent content in Databases on English 5IB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DBMS</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/dbms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/dbms/</guid><description>Database Management System A database management system (DBMS) can store, edit and organise all the data in a database.
It stores data in one central location. It controls who can access and edit the data. It allows data to be shared by many users. It provides user interfaces to work with the data. It automatically creates backups of the data. DBMS offers many significant benefits.
Security: the data is in a safe central location and different access rights can be given to different people.</description></item><item><title>The Databases</title><link>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/the-databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sandra-suozzo.github.io/English5IB/docs/databases/the-databases/</guid><description>The Databases A database is a way of storing large quantities of information so that, using a computer, it can be
searched: to find specific data. sorted (i.e, organised in different ways): to compare data and create reports. Databases have become essential in many different areas of modern life from government and business to science and education. Tax authorities, for example, use databases to keep records of taxpayers and payments, businesses use them to keep customer account and schools use them to maintain student records.</description></item></channel></rss>